Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1927-2010 and undated, bulk 1956-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2011-0013), (9 boxes)
  - Other works (Box 5)
    - A Long and Happy Life
      - Paperback flap copy draft, (2 folders)
      - Edit design, 2008 November 25
      - Handwritten pages, 1958
    - Clear pictures-Design
    - Clear pictures-Acclaim
    - Feasting the Heart-Jeff Anderson's proof, 2000 July 3
    - The Good Priest's son, draft, 2004 September, (4 folders)
    - A Perfect Friend-Pine View School correspondence
    - In Paradise: A Surmise, revised, 2005 September 19
    - The Pleasure of Knowing a Giant Called Ben
    - On Teaching: To the Alumni, 2002 April 12
    - A Lucky Choice
  - Events
    - The Arts Club of Washington: National Award for the Arts-Writing, 2009
    - Invitations to events
    - A Jubilee for Reynolds Price: Duke University, 2008 January 31-2008 February 2
    - Post-Jubilee letters
    - Inauguration of Duke President Nannerln Keohane, 2004
  - Teaching Materials
    - A Weekend with Reynolds Price, 2001
    - Literature and course documents
    - Duke Alumni Affairs, 2002
    - Class assignments
  - Correspondence
    - Electronic, 2006-2008
    - 1953-1962, (4 folders)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 2006-2007
    - Eudora Welty Foundation, 2004-2007
    - Duke University Strategic Plan, 2006 May
    - Trustee/Faculty Committee on Honorary Degrees, 2006 September 29-2007, (2 folders)
    - General, 2005-2007, (7 folders) (Box 6)
    - Correspondence and articles, 2003-2006
    - Civil rights and miscellaneous, 1992-2007
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - Royalty statements, 2005-2007, (2 folders)
    - Various works and printed reading materials, (4 folders)
    - Eudora Welty articles and exhibition, 1999, 2008
    - Scrapbook: extracted articles and clippings, 1986-1993 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, 1986-1994, (2 folders)
    - Magazine articles, 1986-1991
    - Newspaper articles and clippings, 2001-2008
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1994; 2010 and undated
    - Ardent Spirits and miscellaneous photographs, 2007 and undated
  - Finances and graded papers (Box 9)
  - Large version of one of Price's poems (Box OS-16)
- Accession (2011-0080), 1935-2010 and undated, (21 boxes and 1 oversize folder)
  Addition consists of some drafts of Price's writings, particularly materials from Ardent Spirits, as well as academic and teaching materials. The majority of the accession contains personal and general correspondence from throughout Price's life. Other noteworthy materials include miscellaneous clippings and journals, a scrapbook of Price's childhood and student life, and photographs. Also includes a large amount of books from Price's home library in Durham, NC.
  This accession has been minimally processed but has not been interfiled with earlier material.
  Most materials are RESTRICTED until Jan. 20, 2031 and require prior permission for access. Please contact Special Collections with questions about using this material.
  - Correspondence
    - Boatwright, James (Box 1)
    - General Personal Correspondence, 1985-2005, (2 folders)
    - General Personal Correspondence, 2006, (2 of 3 folders)
    - General Personal Correspondence, 2006, (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 2)
    - General Personal Correspondence, 2007, (4 folders)
    - General Personal Correspondence, 2008, (2 folders)
    - General Personal Correspondence, 2009, (2 folders)
    - General Personal Correspondence, 2010
    - Student and Personal Correspondence, 1999-2010, (11 folders)
    - Student and Personal Correspondence, 2004-2007, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Important Personal Correspondence, 1935-1960
    - Important Correspondence: Spender, Stephen, 1950-1970
    - Literary Correspondence and Teaching Materials, 1970-2010, (7 folders)
    - Correspondence, unsorted (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1950s-2000s (Box 21)
    - Correspondence, (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Correspondence and autographs (Box 29)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950s-1990s (Box 29)
  - Teaching Materials
    - Teaching materials, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Notes and manuscripts on Milton and other literary works, (1 of 2 folders)
    - Notes and manuscripts on Milton and other literary works, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Teaching materials (Box 5)
    - Student work/student grades, (3 folders) (Box 21)
    - 50 Years of Teaching at Duke book of letters and clippings (Box 22)
    - Duke teaching, (3 folders) (Box 29)
  - Books from Reynolds Price's library
    Includes both reading copies with annotations by Price, as well as gift copies with inscriptions by others. Many books included loose manuscript pages.
    Some books have been removed for individual cataloging, and are not listed in this finding aid. Their loose pages are included in Box 8, along with notes including the title of the book from which they were removed.
    - Brodhead, Richard H.: The Good of This Place. New Haven: Yale University Press, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Gurganus, Allan: Plays Well With Others. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1997
    - Allison Jr., Dale C.: Resurrecting Jesus. New York: T & T Clark International, 2005
    - Knowles, John: Double Vision. New York: The Macmillan Company, 1964
    - Chappell, Fred: First and Last Words. Baton Rouge: Louisiana State University Press, 1989
    - Price, Reynolds: Good Hearts. New York, New York: Macmillan Publishing Company, 1988
    - Styron, William: The Confessions of Nat Turner. New York: Random House, Inc., 1967
    - Willimon, William H. (editor): Sermons from Duke Chapel. Duke University Press, 2005
    - Fish, Stanely E.: Surprised by Sin: The Reader in Paradise Lost. London: Macmillan and Company Limited, 1967
    - Lee, Harper: To Kill a Mockingbird. New York: HarperCollins Publishers, Inc., 1999
    - Oates, Joyce C.: We Were the Mulvaneys. New York: Penguin Putnam, Inc., 1996
    - Spender, Matthew: From a High Place, A Life of Arshile Gorky. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1999
    - Spender, Stephen: Collected Poems, 1928-1953. London: Faber and Faber Limited, 1955
    - Hemingway, Ernest: A Farewell to Arms. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1929
    - Rilke, Rainer M.: The Life of the Virgin Mary (translated by Stephen Spender). London: Vision Pres Limited, 1951
    - Schiff, James A.: Understanding Reynolds Price. Columbia, South Carolina: University of South Carolina Press, 1996
    - The Red Letter New Testament of Our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ. Philadelphia: International Press, 1941
    - Styron, William: The Long March. New York: Random House, Inc., 1952
    - Woolf, Virginia: Between the Acts. Rome: The Albatross, 1850
    - Faulkner, William: Pylon. New York: Random House, Inc., 1967
    - Humpfreys, Josephine: The Fireman's Fair. New York: Penguin Books USA, 1991
    - Humpfreys, Josephine: Dreams of Sleep. New York: The Viking Press, 1984
    - Humpferys, Josephine: Rich in Love. New York: Viking Penguin, Inc., 1987
    - Woolf, Virginia: To the Lighthouse. New York: Harcourt, Brace & World, Inc., 1955 (Box 8)
    - Price, Reynolds: A Long and Happy Life. New York: Atheneum, 1962
    - Knowles, John: A Separate Peace. New York: The Macmillan Company, 1959
    - Buechner, Frederick: A Long Day's Dying. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1950
    - Baker, Raymond F.: Andersonville, The Story of a Civil War Prison Camp. Washington: U.S. Department of the Interior, 1972
    - Welty, Eudora: The Collected Stories of Eudora Welty. New York: Harcourt, Brace, Jovanovich, 1980
    - Spender, Stephen: Engaged in Writing and The Fool and the Prince. London: Hamish Hamilton Ltd., 1958
    - Welty, Eudora: Delta Wedding. New York: Harcourt, Brace & World, 1946
    - Henry III, William A.: "The Mind Roams Free." TIME Magazine. Vol. 143 No. 21. 27 May 1994
    - Price, Reynolds: "A Waiting Beauty." Allure Magazine. November 2002
    - The 1947 Warrentonian. Warrenton, North Carolina. John Graham High School, 1947
    - The 1951 Warrentonain (Volume V). Warrenton, North Carolina. John Graham High School, 1951
    - Weber, Bruce: Bear Pond. New York: Bullfinch Press, 1990
    - Miscellaneous Removed Papers from Printed Materials and Publications "unappraised", 1958-1980
    - Papers Removed from (unappraised) Printed Materials and Publications. Correspondence and Poetry, 1955-2008
    - Papers Removed from (appraised) Printed Materials and Publications. Correspondence, 1970-2010
    - Papers Removed from (appraised) Printed Materials and Publications. Annotations and Clippings, 1954-1963
    - Note Removed from D.H. Lawrence Women In Love.
    - Smith, Grover: The Waste Land. London: George Allen & Unwin, Ltd., 1983 (Box 9)
    - Binding, Paul: The Still Moment, Eudora Welty, Portrait of a Writer. London: Virago Press Ltd. 1994
    - Pollard, Josephine: Wonderful Stories of the Bible. The Saalfield Publishing Company, 1925
    - Eliot, T.S.: The Family Reunion (Introduction and Commentrary by Nevil Coghill). London: Faber and Faber Ltd., 1969
    - Valdez, Michael: The Novel and Globalization of Culture. New York: Oxford University Press, 1995
    - Kreyling, Michael: Figures of the Hero in Southern Narrative. Baton Rouge: Louisiana State University Press, 1987
    - Blackburn, William: Lady Magdalen Herbert and Her Son George. The South Atlantic Quarterly. Vol. 50, No. 3. July 1951
    - The North Carolina Historical Review. Vol. XLIX, No. 1. North Carolina State Department of Archives and History. January, 1972.
    - Nikulin, N.: Lucas Cranach. Masters of World Painting. Leningrad: Aurora Art Publishers, 1976 (inscription and drawing by Allan Gurganus)
    - Coghill, Nevill: Langland: Piers Plowman. London: Longmans, Green & Co. Ltd., 1964
    - Aiken, Conrad: Selected Poems of Emily Dickinson. New York: The Modern Library, 1948
    - Dean, Leaonard D. (editor): The College Omnibus. 7th Edition. 1951
    - Price, Reynolds: The Good Priest's Son (Advance uncorrected proof). New York: Scribner, 2005
    - Harrison, G.B. (general editor): Major British Writers. Volumes I & II. New York: Harcourt, Brace and Company, 1954
    - Harrison, G.B. (editor): Shakespeare, The Complete Works. Harcourt, Brace and Company, 1952
    - Lubbock, Percy: The Craft of Fiction. Jonathan Cape, 1954
    - Keats, John: Selected Poems and Letters. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company, 1952
    - Culler, A. Dwight (editor): Poetry and Criticism of Matthew Arnold. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company, 1961
    - Frost, William (editor): English Masterpieces, The Age of Chaucer. New Jersey, Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1955
    - Anderson, Carl L.: Williams, George W. British and American Essays, 1950-1956. New York, Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1959
    - Dickens, Charles: Great Expectations, 1958
    - Shakespeare, William: King Lear, 1958
    - The Plays of Christoper Marlowe. The World's Classics, 1950
    - Dumont, Henri: El Greco. New York: The Hyperion Press, Inc., 1948
    - Papers removed from printed materials and publications
    - Latham, Agnes M.C.: The Poems of Sir Walter Raleigh. Cambridge: Harvard University Press, 1951 (from William Blackburn) (Box 10)
    - The Complete Poems of D.H. Lawrence (Vol I). London: William Heinemann Ltd., 1957 (from Stephen Spender)
    - Grierson, Herbert J.C.: Metaphysical Lyrics & Poems of the Seventeenth Century. Oxford: Oxford University Press, 1921 (from William Blackburn)
    - Clark, James M.: Holbein's Dance of Death. London: Phaidon Press Ltd., 1947 (from brother "Will" Price)
    - Yarmolinski, Avrahm: The Portable Chekhov. New York: The Viking Press, 1947 (from William Blackburn)
    - Cameron, Norman: A Season in Hell (Rimbaud). London: John Lehmann, 1949 (from Stephen Spender)
    - Tin House Magazine, Vol 9, No. 4. Portland: McCormack Comunications LLC, Summer 2008 (from Allan Gurganus)
    - The Oxford Book of Italian Verse, XIII Century-XIX Century. Clarendon Press, 1952 (from Stephen Spender)
    - Stevens Holly: Wallace Stevens, The Palm at the End of the Mind. Selected Poems and a Play. New York, Random House Inc., 1972 (from Laird and Francoise)
    - Fishwick, Marshall: General Lee's Photographer, The Life and Work of Michael Miley. New York: The University of North Carolina Press, 1954 (from Eudora Welty)
    - Perkins, David: The News and Observer's Raleigh, A Living History of North Carolina's Capital. Winston-Salem: John F. Blair, 1994 (from David Perkins)
    - Miller, Gilbert: Vivian Leigh and Laurence Oliver in Caesar and Cleopatra (Shaw); Anthony and Cleopatra (Shakespeare). Laurence Olivier Productions, 1974
    - Aperture No. 81. New York: Aperture Inc., 1978 (from Eudora Welty; publication includes her photos)
    - Dunwell, Steve: Duke, A Portrait. Durham: Duke University, 1983 (from Duke University stores employees)
    - Spender, Natasha: An English Garden in Provence. London: The Harvill Press, 1999 (from Natasha Spender)
    - Brown, Lightning A.: Pink Trash (electronic copy of book and various poems), 1995 (from author)
    - Whigham, Peter: The Poems of Catullus. England: Penguin Books Ltd., 1966
    - Auden, W.H.: George Gordon, Lord Byron; Selected Poetry and Prose. New York: The New American Library, 1966 (typed copy of Byron's last poem)
    - Hayward, John: John Donne, A Selection of His Poetry. England: Penguin Books Ltd., 1955 (signed)
    - Wright, David: Beowulf. England: Penguin Books Ltd., 1957 (annotated)
    - Alexander, Michael: Beowulf. England: Penguin Books Ltd., 1973 (annotated)
    - Williams, Oscar: A Little Treasury of Modern Poetry (Revised Edition). New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1950
    - Ward, Charles A.: Oracles of Nostradamus. New York: Random House Inc., 1940 (inside cover note by Reynolds Price)
    - Tolstoy, Leo: Resurrection. Oxford: Oxford University Press, 1956 (manuscript paper inside)
    - Hadas, Moses: Three Greek Romances. New York: The Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc., 1953
    - Price, Reynolds: The Good News According to Mark, 1976 (for friends at Christmas 1976)
    - Morris, Pamela: The Diary of a Country Priest by Georges Bernanos. New York: The Macmillan Company, 1962
    - Mendelson, Edward: The English Auden: Peoms, Essays and Dramatic Writings 1927-1939. London: Faber and Faber Ltd., 1977
    - Fitzgerald, Robert: The Odyssey. New York: Anchor Press, 1961
    - Fletcher, Harris F.: The Complete Poetical Works of John Milton. Cambridge: Houghton Mifflin Company, 1941 (inside cover note and drawing by Reynolds Price)
    - Farrer, Katherine: The Cretan Counterfeit. England: Penguin Books Ltd., 1955
    - Steegmuller, Francis: Madame Bovary (Flaubert). New York: Random House Inc., 1957 (
    - Zabel, Morton D.: Lord Jim (Conrad). Cambridge: Houghton Mifflin Company, 1958
    - Campbell, Roy: Poems of Baudelaire. New Tork: Pantheon Books Inc., 1952
    - Kramer, Larry: Faggots, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Salter, James: A Sport and a Pastime, 1967
    - Price, Bobby: The View from the Void, 2010
    - Cameron, Ron, ed.: The Other Gospels, 1982
    - Martin, Eric B.: The Virgin's Guide to Mexico, 2007 (note and signature from author) (Box 23)
    - The Archive, Vol. 108 No. 2, Spring 1996 (Duke University undergraduate creative-writing publication)
    - Salter, James: A Sport and a Pastime, 1967 (Paris Review Books edition, New York; note and signature from author)
    - Spender, Stephen (ed.): W.H. Auden: A Tribute, 1975 (note and signature from Spender)
    - Cecil, David: The Cecils of Hatfield House, 1973 (note and signature from author)
    - The Brilliance of Birds: The Sculpture of Grainger McKoy, 2007 (note and signature from McKoy--note is not written on the book's pages but on a card that has been inserted in the book)
    - Price, Reynolds: Letter to a Godchild, 2006
    - Price, Reynolds: A Serious Way of Wondering, 2003
    - Empson, William: Milton's God, 1965 (note and signature from author)
    - Wood, Gerald C. (ed.): Selected One-Act Plays of Horton Foote, 1989 (note and signature from Foote)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne: The Collected Stories, 1970
    - Segal, Lore and Randall Jarrell (trans.): The Juniper Tree and Other Tales from Grimm, 1973
    - Darien, Peter: Ecliptic, ca. 1969 (note and signature from author)
    - Watson, Sterling: Weep No More My Brother, 1978 (note and signature from author)
    - Phillips, J.B. (trans.): The Young Church in Action: A Translation of the Acts of the Apostles, 1957 (a note on a card inserted into the book indicates that this book was once given as a gift to Blue Calhoun from a group called the "QCA Cabinet")
    - Wagenknecht, Edward: Geraldine Farrar: An Authorized Record of Her Career, 1929 (from a limited run of 350 copies that were signed by Geraldine Farrar; inserted in the book is correspondence between Price and the book's author, as well as correspondence from various record collector services to which Price had evidently inquired about acquiring some of Farrar's rarer recordings)
    - Lasky, Jesse L. with Pat Silver: Love Scene: The Story of Laurence Olivier and Vivien Leigh, 1978 (inside the book there is a pen drawing with the caption, "To Reynolds From Allan 1979 Happy Birthday")
    - Penna, Sandro: Poesie, 1957 (inscribed, "To Reynolds from Stephen May 1962 Rome")
    - Hauerwas, Stanley: Prayers Plainly Spoken, 1999 (note and signature from author; also, an undated letter from Hauerwas to Price has been inserted in the book)
    - Price, Reynolds: The Tongues of Angels, 1990
    - Parker, Harold T. and Marvin L. Brown, Jr.: Major Themes in Modern European History: An Invitation to Inquiry and Reflection (Vol. 1), 1974 (note and signature from Parker)
    - Latipac, Needham B. Broughton High School yearbook, 1951 (Box 24)
    - Miller, Evelyn Ellison: A Clay Inheritance, 2008
    - Kitto, H.D.F.: Form and Meaning in Drama: A Study of Six Greek Plays and of Hamlet, 1956
    - Tighe, Marie Kevin: Arch, Steeples, and Dome, 2009 (note and signature from author)
    - An Anthology of Modern Japanese Poetry, 1957 (includes undated note about the poems, with no signature)
    - Price, Reynolds: A Long and Happy Life (in Japanese), 1961 (inscribed, "To Reynolds Price with love and faith," from the translator, 1970)
    - The Atlantic, Vol. 167, No. 2, Feb. 1941
    - Spender, Stephen: Journals 1939-1983, 1985 (inscribed to Reynolds, Nov. 1985)
    - Hurlbut, Charles: Story of the Bible, 1932
    - The Archive, Vol. 88, No. 1, Fall 1975
    - Price, Reynolds: The Surface of Earth, 1975
      Includes note: "This is the copy from which all future editions should be set. A list of pages needing correction is on the first white page from the back. Reynolds Price, 29 Jan. 1976."
    - Kepler, Thomas: Pathways to Spiritual Power, 1952
    - New Testament (New International Version)
    - New Testament and Psalms
    - Various titles, unsorted and unlisted (Box 26)
  - Scrapbooks, albums, and diaries
    - Scrapbook of Price's childhood (Box 6)
    - Leaves of Gold, a book of poetry given to Price by his mother, 1948 (Box 12)
      Includes inscription wishing him a "long, useful, happy life."
    - Scrapbook from Price's years at Duke University
    - Scrapbook of theater and movie clippings and programs
    - Scrapbook of opera clippings
    - Photo album with family pictures, etc., from Price's childhood
    - 3 scrapbooks of entertainment clippings, focusing on Ingrid Bergman, Vivien Leigh, and Greta Garbo, among others (Box 13)
    - Scrapbook/album of Price as a child, with school projects and drawings, as well as WWII clippings
    - Sketchbook of drawings from 1985
    - School project, "Constructions"
    - Notebook, kept by Price, 1992-1993
    - Baby album of Price (Box 14)
    - Photo album, including WWI photographs, 1904-1921
    - Photo album with albumen portraits, including Abraham Lincoln, 1800s
    - Diary of Sallie B. Taylor, Frenchtown, NJ, 1897
    - Day planners/agenda books, 1959-1984, 2009 (Box 15)
    - Roladex cards
    - Logs, 1977-1982 (3 books)
    - Diaries (incomplete), 1961-1962, 1988, 1998
    - Poetry books, 1957 and 2003
    - Day planners/agenda books, 1985-2008 (Box 24)
  - Photographs
    - Miscellaneous photographs, (8 folders) (Box 4)
    - Family and childhood photographs
    - Oxford, Europe and USA, 1956, (4 folders)
    - Ardent Sprit photographs
    - Negatives (Box 14)
    - Snapshots, unsorted (Box 16)
    - Snapshots, unsorted (Box 17)
    - Portraits of Price
    - Old snapshots, other treasures
    - Miscellaneous negatives
    - De-framed photographs from Price's home, Durham, NC, (4 folders) (Box 18)
    - Art photos
    - Theater groups
    - Family photos
    - Mike Jordan and others
    - Groups
    - Portraits of Price
    - Photographs from Price's books (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous snapshots and negatives, (14 folders) (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous snapshots and negatives (Box 28)
    - Photographs from Price's home in Durham (Box 28)
    - Oversize photographs and posters (Box 30)
    - Photographs (Box OS-16)
    - Photographs (Box OS-16)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1955-2006 (Box 4)
    - Journals
    - Miscellaneous items
    - Address and phone books
    - The Latipac (Needham B. Broughton High School Yearbook), 1948-1950 (Box 5)
    - Diplomas (Duke, Oxford) (Box 18)
    - Rare book purchases, 1976-1999 (Box 20)
    - Clear Pictures
    - Scrapbook pages of clippings, some poems
    - Genealogy of the Walters, Mayfield, and Kendal families (Box 21)
    - Oxford University printed materials, 1955
    - Duke University commencement planning, 2007
    - Confidential files, (2 folders)
    - Calendar pages, 1962 and 1984
    - Halloween readings, Duke University, 1998-2005
    - Voice exercise therapy
    - Awards
    - Edward C. Price's Bible
    - Cabin 16 plaque, from camp
    - Autograph collection materials, 1950
    - North Carolina Literary Hall of Fame, 2002 (videotape)
    - Charlie Rose: A Conversation with Reynolds Price, Gardner Taylor, and Lorenzo Albacete, December 14, 2001 (DVD)
    - Price's fraternity paddle, Duke University (Box 25)
    - Price's U.S. passports (Box 27)
    - Price's DVD inventory (Box 29)
    - Merton College, Oxford ephemera (Box 29)
    - Caretaker directions, 2007 (Box 29)
    - A Separate Peace production information, 1972 (Box 29)
    - Duke agreement, 1972 (Box 29)
    - Geraldine Farrar (Box 29)
    - Genealogy photocopies (Box 29)
    - Postcard collection (Box 32)
    - Souvenir of Abraham Lincoln's hair (Box OS-16)
  - Writings
    - Ardent Spirits (Box 1)
      - Part One first revision, January 2005, (3 folders)
      - Draft (revised 20 November 2006), (3 folders)
      - Draft: Oxford
      - Revision, 25 May 2006, (3 folders)
      - First draft, 17 October 2005, (2 folders)
      - Proposal drafts and miscellaneous revisions, 2005-2006
    - Ardent Spirits, (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Gospel of Mark
    - Mark
    - John Milton
    - Near the Cove (memoir of Israel), 1983, (4 folders)
    - The Good Priest's Son, (8 folders)
    - Poems
    - Short Stories, book 1
    - Notes, LHL
    - Roxanna Slade (screenplay)
    - Private Contentment, 1982
    - Notes
    - Mary Stuart (adapted by Stephen Spender)
    - Writings and speeches by Price, (7 folders) (Box 20)
    - Journal of a trip to Israel, by Jeffrey Anderson, 1980-1981
    - Preface 3A, Ardent Spirits
    - Dear Harper, a letter concerning faith, (2 folders)
    - The Night of the Little House by Eudora Welty
    - The Tongues of Angels screenplay, 1991, (2 folders)
    - A Long and Happy Life screenplay, (2 folders)
    - Ardent Spirits, (4 folders)
    - According to Mark, (2 folders)
    - Notes on plays, etc., 1991
    - Eudora Welty: A House Revived, by Price
    - Screenplay/script, no name
    - Good News: The 4 Gospels, by Price